Captain's log. Stardate,
National Donut Day.
We're under attack from a
ship made of solid fire.
All weapons simply pass through
and come out the other end.
Like that ball bearing I
once mistook for a mint.
It's a conundrum, Kif.
Pray fetch my travel tub.
I do my best thinking
in the shower.
humming
Ya ba bum
Ya ba bum bum bum
Could you at
least close the curtain, sir?
Certainly.
Lieutenant Kroker!
You expect me to think
without a loofah?
Where's my loofah?
- What loofah?
- You! You're the loofah.
Will you be quiet?
I'm trying to think!
Ah-ha! Water!
Fire's mortal enemy!
Lieutenant, fire water.
What the? Who used
up all the water?
- Your shower depleted the
ship's three-year supply, sir.
Well, no worries.
I can end this battle
with two words.
"We surrender."
Sign
this certificate of defeat,
so I can show my mom.
- Kif, my desk.
I'll just put the old
Zapp Hancock on it.
Big confident dot on the I.
Oh-ho. You're juicier
than I thought, Kif.
- I have had it!
I'm through putting up with
your... crap!
I'm filing a formal complaint!
- It's pronounced compliment.
- And now, I am proud to present
the monthly Only Good
Employee of the Month Award.
Yay.
- This month's recipient
has the special distinction
of also having won the
award every previous month.
- Do you think it's me?
- Congratulations!
- Well done, Leela.
You've reached the
pinnacle of success
in the stagnant, dead-end
delivery business.
- You've really hit rock top!
- Thanks, everybody.
It's a dream come true.
A recurring dream. That
I can't wake up from.
Who wants cake?
There's one handful
left. I'll have it.
- I call this disciplinary
hearing to order.
Captain Brannigan, Lieutenant
Kroker has made some serious,
though somewhat
amusing, allegations.
Do you have counsel?
- I say, I say, present!
- Lieutenant Kroker,
do you have counsel?
You're representing
both sides in this case?
- Till my wings give
out, Your Honor.
- I'm going to allow this.
- Now, Mr. Kroker,
please describe
the horrific
treatment you endured
at the hands of my innocent
other client there.
- He took a public
shower and used me to...
scrub his armpit.
- It was a joke.
Literally everyone was
laughing except Kif.
- He insisted on telling me
his fantasies about my wife!
- That was just
locker room talk.
- He wore greenface!
- It was a Halloween costume.
- He made me watch him
perform an erotic fan dance
with a ping-pong paddle
and a no-show sock.
- It was a different time!
- It was yesterday!
- So you admit it!
- Your Honor, I have
reached a verdict.
I find my client,
Zapp Brannigan,
guilty.
- I'm going to allow this.
Captain Brannigan, there is
no room in this organization
for bullying and harassment.
Your egregious behavior
cannot...
Why are you massaging me?
- You just seem so tense.
Also, you should smile more.
You're prettier when you smile.
See? It's just
nicer for everyone.
- It is therefore
this court's judgment
that you face the
ultimate penalty.
- Dating a woman over 35?
- Zapp Brannigan, you
are hereby... canceled.
The second-worst punishment.
- You will be
stripped of your title
while you undergo mandatory
sensitivity training.
And for the duration
of your cancellation,
you shall wear the Scarlet C.
- I object to these
frivolous, paltry charges.
- Frivolous poultry?
You insult me, sir!
Who is it? Poop?
- Captain Turanga Leela,
you put in an application
to be a DOOP pilot?
- Uh, yeah. Like an hour ago.
- You're hired.
- Captain of the Nimbus!
So you're gonna be Kif's
commanding lobster?
- Negative. Right?
- Affirmative. I'm
taking some family leave,
so I can get bossed
around by someone I like.
- Psst. Stinky needs changing.
- But the DOOP did
authorize me to bring along
two trusted crew members.
A first officer,
which, in a bold
command decision,
will be Fry.
- Aw, thanks, honey.
- I mean, Captain Honey.
- Sir.
- And a Chief Science Officer.
Professor...
- I, Bender, humbly accept
this prestigious appointment.
Also, it comes
with double salary.
- So long and good
luck, you three.
You have been an important part
of the Planet Express family,
and you'll be greatly missed.
Next item of
business. We have...
one, two, three office
chairs for sale.
- I'm here for the
sensitivity training,
and, uh, also, do you have
a better-looking sister?
- Please go inside
and take a seat.
The training will begin shortly.
- Howdy, cancel mates.
You wanna know why
I got sent here?
- Nope.
- Indecent exposure!
You all saw it,
right? You wanna see it again?
- I could barely see
it the first time.
What?!
I've seen brighter.
- Yeah, well, it's not
about the brightness.
It's about the
color temperature!
- How 'bout you?
What did you do?
- Meh, it was total BS.
Some people "alleged"
I was verbally abusive
and threw food at my coworkers.
I mean, a lot of
people, actually.
- That's ridiculous.
You're obviously not
the type to waste food.
- You should talk, you
family-sized bucket of lard-ass!
Ow!
That hurt in more ways than one.
It hurt in two
ways.
- Hello, class. I'm Dr. Kind,
your sensitivity instructor.
- Wow, you're ugly.
- Oh! Now, we don't
talk that way in here.
This is a safe space.
The fact is, sometimes,
our words hurt other people,
and we need to be made
aware of how that feels.
It feels like this!
- Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow!
- This isn't some
woke-ass seminar!
This course will take the form
of a simulated space mission,
with me as your abusive captain!
And you'll learn from the
example I'm not setting!
- Ouch!
Now, kindly
follow me to the simulator.
Ooh, careful. There's a step.
This
mission may be simulated,
but my abuse will be very real.
Set course for degradation!
- Hm, never been
there. Sounds exotic.
- I'm pleased to have a civilian
pilot of your caliber, Leela.
The DOOP is rebranding
to project an image
of peaceful exploration
rather than war.
Also, we want to show we care about
looking like we care about hiring women.
Wow, it's huge!
It's like a Princess cruise
ship with laser cannons!
- I hope they have
a kids' center.
- They don't.
But there's a buffet with
all-you-can-eat week-old sashimi.
- Score!
LEELA
I'm really nervous.
What if I can't handle this?
Leela, I
know absolutely nothing,
but I know one thing.
You'll be great.
- Nimbus crew, I'm
pleased to introduce
Zapp Brannigan's replacement,
Captain Turanga Leela.
- At ease, crew.
I, um, I know I'm nothing
like Zapp Brannigan, but I...
Dear Captain's Diary.
If you're not me,
don't read this.
We're preparing to
make first contact
with a primitive civilization.
Anyway, G2G. TTYL.
PS, Fry looks cute.
- Captain, it's time to
descend to the planet.
Have you readied
a shuttle-copter?
- I've been thinking about that.
Maybe we shouldn't
intimidate them
with our advanced technology.
- Hm...
Generally, I like to
intimidate new civilizations,
but what did you have in mind?
- A bucket on a rope.
Sorry you can't come, Bender.
Your robot technology
might scare them.
Safe travels.
- This was a clever
idea, Captain.
- See, Leela?
You're doing great.
- Hope my robot technology
isn't scaring you.
And now, to stop it.
- Hello! We are people from
the sky who come in peace.
They speak Tactillian.
- Ah!
- I am Airee, Quing
of Planet Tactillia.
For centuries, we have wondered
if we are alone in the universe.
But now, we know
intelligent life exists,
flying among the
stars in a bucket.
Welcome.
- The bucket people have
unusual bodies, oh Quing.
- They have fewer
knobs, but not none!
- Hey! Just 'cause I'm
wearing a short skirt.
No means no.
- Blech! What are
you doing? Stop that!
- Captain! Respect
their customs!
We need to win the hearts
and knobs of these people.
But they're so grabby. Oops!
Whee!
- Um... Quing Airee,
we have important
matters to discuss,
but it may be difficult.
Our civilizations are at very
different levels of technology.
- No kidding. You
traveled in a bucket.
- Actually, that was...
- We have much to teach you.
Brush harder, tubby!
- You can't yell at me.
You're on your short arms.
- I yell at any height I want!
You! Brush your teeth!
- I don't have teeth.
- Then brush my teeth!
Damn,
those are nice...
Whoa!
You all think
you've humiliated your crews.
You ain't seen nothin'.
I'm gonna do
something so degrading
that you'll never be the same!
I'm going to take a shower...
right here on the bridge!
- You sicken me.
- If you're wondering
how our civilization
became so advanced...
- We're not, but...
- it's because we learned to
harness pneumatic technology.
All the sophisticated
machinery you see
is powered by air.
- I've heard of air.
- This is our main
air power plant.
The air blows through
high-pressure transmission lines,
so our citizens can
power their appliances
and inflate their meals.
- I'm fascinated by
all this wonderful air.
Where does it come from?
- I'm glad you asked.
Behold!
Oh no, wait. Hang
on.
Behold!
The Great Blow Hole!
- Fresh from the hole.
Whoa!
This is kinda fun.
- Get out of our air!
- This is an amazing natural
resource, Quing Airee.
You should do everything in
your power to protect it.
- Uh, Leela, a word.
I may not have told you
everything about this mission.
These people are
lovely and whatever.
It's debatable.
We're really here for the air.
- What?
The whole core of
this planet is frozen gas.
It's like a slot machine
that keeps paying out air!
- That sounds like a
really boring casino.
- Have you been to space, Leela?
Not a lotta air out there,
and what we do have
is, like, 50% burp.
Which is why you must get
them to sign this treaty
granting us air rights.
So,
this peace mission isn't
really about peace?
- Who said it's not about peace?
It's entirely about peace.
Also, air.
Leela, sometimes we
coerce people with war.
Other times, we
take the high road
and trick them with peace.
Excuse me.
- It is my great pleasure
to sign this peace
treaty with Captain Leela
and her big bucket
of space friends.
- Tradition dictates
that the parties begin
with the ritual knobbling.
- Uh...
- Our captain will gladly
engage in the knobbling.
- I will? I'd rather not.
I said knobble!
Blech!
It's starting to get
real ripe in here.
- No offense, but could it
possibly be all the food you threw?
Let's
find out.
- Ow.
- Man. It does stink.
It's like rotten flesh
floating in a puddle of vomit.
You wish.
It's a durian!
- No.
Noooo!
What's a durian, by the way?
- Earth's most putrid
yet delicious fruit.
So refreshing after
a public shower.
- My God. It actually
has stink lines.
- Tough it out, snowflake!
Now you see how you've
demoralized your own crews!
Crews you expect to
follow you into battle!
- At least with me in charge,
they don't suffer long.
- Let's see how well you
fight under these conditions.
Crew to simulated
battle stations!
Captain Cranky!
90 degrees to starboard!
Shields up, Flashnut!
Fire simulated
missile, you fat moron!
So mean.
That simulated ship looks
a bit like my real ship,
the Nimbus.
Yes! Direct hit!
Now, who's the fat,
incontinent moron?
- Hey, man, that's catchy!
What song is that playing
on the emergency siren?
- It's the emergency
siren! We're under attack!
- Ah! I'm getting outta here!
- We need this treaty, Leela.
Act like a captain and
start fondling knobs.
On behalf of the
Democratic Order of Planets,
it is my honor to, respectfully,
grope your slimy...
I can't do it.
Something just seems
inappropriate.
Possibly this thing.
- What a marvelous bucket.
- Jumping Judas.
I've never seen a
simulation so realistic.
Is it "okay" to hit
on a simulation?
- What is the meaning of this?
I thought I canceled
all four of you!
- Yes, but I hijacked this ship
after hog-tying your pathetic
sensitivity instructor!
- It was a teachable moment.
- So, our ship was real?
And the simulation
was simulated?
- No one cancels Dr. Gary Kind.
- Who's the tall short guy?
- Dr. Gary Kind,
one of the DOOP's most
notorious gropers.
A groper?
- Now, this
gentleman's a diplomat.
- You messed with the wrong
doctor of botanical science.
But I have with me a bio-weapon
of inconceivable power!
- He's got something
in his jacket!
And so do I!
- Jeez. How many more
durians does this guy have?
- One. Enough to befoul
this planet's air supply
for centuries!
- Gary, put down the durian.
We swore never to use
those in peacetime.
- Bender to Leela! The Nimbus came
under attack about an hour ago!
I probably should
have called earlier.
Be on the lookout
for a small gunship
about yea big from a
million miles away.
- Captain Leela, command the
Nimbus to fire on Dr. Kind.
But, he's surrounded
by those poor innocent pervs.
They might get hurt.
What a wimp!
Captains need to be ruthless.
Women belong in the kitchen,
fixing me a sweet durian pie.
- That's an
offensive stereotype.
Leela's terrible at baking.
Your eight-hour
sensitivity training is complete.
Please deposit me in the
nearest recycling bin.
- No chance.
- Zapp Brannigan, having
completed your rehabilitation,
I hereby reinstate you
as Captain of the Nimbus.
Order your ship to fire!
- Uh, thank you, Glab,
but, uh, I'm not
sure I can do that.
Dr. Kind taught me a lot.
- That's wonderful!
- I now know there's a difference
between right and wrong.
One of them gets you canceled.
- See what you get
with PC culture?
Weak captains too cowardly
to shoot the helpless!
- Ah, what a beautiful night
for smell-gazing.
- You should have shot me before
I destroyed your precious air!
If I were captain, I'd have
fired without a second thought!
Your eight-hour
sensitivity training is complete.
Please deposit me...
- Dr. Kind, having completed
your rehabilitation,
I name you Captain of the
Nimbus. Order your ship to...
- Fire!
- Leela, you're a hero!
- Quing Airee, I am now
prepared to knobble.
Don't mind the
durian.
- I declare the groping
optional. Where do I sign?
- In conclusion,
I sincerely apologize
to all those I've harmed.
Especially Kif Kroker,
the giant sex
ladies of Amazonia,
simulated Leela,
and, of course,
the late Dr. Kind.
Yeah, baby!
- Move! This ceremony
is for Leela.
Captain Leela,
having heroically secured
our supply of space air,
I present you the
DOOP's highest honor,
the Medal of Valor.
- It's pronounced velour.
- Your refusal to shoot
unarmed civilians when ordered
was an inspiration to us all,
as well as grounds for a
dishonorable discharge!
What do you think this is,
the Peace Corps? Get out!
- I guess I just don't have what
it takes to be a DOOP captain.
- No, you have something better.
You have what it
takes to be Leela.
- Yum. Durian!
May I slurp your cheek clean
with my tendrils?
- Eh, sure. And thanks
for asking first.
Ew, blech!
But also yum.